A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1959
  - Colombia, 1959/311
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1959/311.E
      - A-S (Reel 34, Frame 250)
  - Costa Rica, 1959/313
    - Cordero Rojas, Alvaro (Reel 34, Frame 316)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, 1959/313.E
      - Carvajal, Jose F. (Reel 34, Frame 321)
  - Cuba, 1959/315
    Cuba
    - M-V (Reel 34, Frame 324)
  - Ecuador, 1959/317
    - A-U (Reel 34, Frame 353)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, 1959/317.E
      - Miranda M., Heleodoro (Reel 34, Frame 389)
  - Guatemala, 1959/319
    - F-U (Reel 34, Frame 402)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/319.D
      - Agriculture (Motta, Roberto) (Reel 34, Frame 426)
  - Haiti, 1959/320
    - C-U (Reel 34, Frame 430)
    - Haiti - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/320.D
      - Agriculture (Philippeaux, Gerard) (Reel 34, Frame 454)
    - Haiti - Fellowships, 1959/320.E
      - Pinchinat, Antonio (Reel 34, Frame 462)
  - Honduras, 1959/321
    - Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Reel 34, Frame 466)
    - Health (Vidal Ramos, Luis) (Reel 34, Frame 683)
  - Mexico, 1959/323
    - 323 (Reel 34, Frame 687)
    - A-I (Reel 34, Frame 693)
    - L-M (Reel 34, Frame 840)
    - N-T (Reel 34, Frame 1019)
    - U (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1959/323.A
      - N-U (Reel 35, Frame 102)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1959/323.E
      - 323E (Reel 35, Frame 127)
      - A-T (Reel 35, Frame 166)
    - Mexico - Yellow Fever, 1959/323.O
      - 323O (Reel 35, Frame 238)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1959/323.R
      - D-U (Reel 35, Frame 243)
  - Nicaragua, 1959/325
    - Porras M., Edmundo (Reel 35, Frame 269)
    - Nicaragua - Medical Sciences, 1959/325.A
      - University of Nicaragua (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 272)
  - Republic of Panama, 1959/327
    - Shelokov, Alexis I. (Reel 35, Frame 274)
  - Paraguay, 1959/329
    - C-R (Reel 35, Frame 276)
    - Paraguay - Medical Sciences, 1959/329.A
      - University of Asuncion (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 294)
    - Paraguay - Nursing, 1959/329.C
      - 329C (Reel 35, Frame 358)
  - Peru, 1959/331
    - B-Z (Reel 35, Frame 364)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1959/331.A
      - University (S) (Reel 35, Frame 472)
    - Peru - Nursing, 1959/331.C
      - 331C (Reel 35, Frame 496)
      - National Institute of Nursing, Lima (Reel 35, Frame 501)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/331.D
      - Agriculture (Labarthe C., Enrique) (Reel 35, Frame 503)
    - Peru - Fellowships, 1959/331.E
      - M-R (Reel 35, Frame 558)
    - Peru - Humanities and Arts, 1959/331.R
      - National Library of Peru (Reel 35, Frame 580)
    - Peru - Virus Studies, 1959/331.V
      - 331V (Reel 35, Frame 616)
  - El Salvador, 1959/333
    - Trejos, Alfonso (Reel 35, Frame 646)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/333.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 35, Frame 650)
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, 1959/333.E
      - Hasbun, E. Roberto (Reel 35, Frame 667)
  - Uruguay, 1959/337
    - B-U (Reel 35, Frame 671)
    - Uruguay - Medical Sciences, 1959/337.A
      - University of Montevideo (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 709)
    - Uruguay - Nursing, 1959/337.C
      - University of Montevideo (Nursing School) (Reel 35, Frame 736)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/337.D
      - University of Montevideo (Poultry Pathology) (Reel 35, Frame 740)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, 1959/337.E
      - B-R (Reel 35, Frame 765)
  - Venezuela, 1959/339
    - A-V (Reel 35, Frame 802)
    - Venezuela - Medical Sciences, 1959/339.A
      - University of Carabobo (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 931)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/339.D
      - A-U (Reel 35, Frame 933)
    - Venezuela - Declinations, 1959/339.F
      - University of Venezuela (Library) (Reel 35, Frame 971)
  - Great Britain, 1959/400
    - Commonwealth Institute of Biological Control (Reel 35, Frame 992)
  - England, 1959/401
    - A-B (Reel 35, Frame 997)
    - C-F (Reel 35, Frame 1105)
    - G-K (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - L (Reel 36, Frame 105)
    - M-P (Reel 36, Frame 291)
    - University of Leeds (Toulmin, Stephen E.) (Reel 36, Frame 508)
    - University of Leeds (D-W) (Reel 36, Frame 634)
    - University (B-S) (Reel 36, Frame 640)
    - Q-W (Reel 36, Frame 849)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1959/401.A
      - M-U (Reel 36, Frame 1007)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/401.D
      - University of Cambridge (Zoology) (Reel 36, Frame 1013)
    - England - Fellowships, 1959/401.E
      - D-W (Reel 36, Frame 1020)
    - England - Declinations, 1959/401.F
      - Dore, Ron P. (Reel 36, Frame 1076)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1959/401.R
      - 401R (Reel 36, Frame 1085)
      - British Broadcasting Corporation (Holroyde, Persy) (Reel 36, Frame 1089)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1959/401.S
      - N-O (Reel 36, Frame 1095)
  - Ireland, 1959/403
    - O-U (Reel 37, Frame 1)
  - Scotland, 1959/405
    - E-U (Reel 37, Frame 128)
    - Scotland - Fellowships, 1959/405.E
      - F-M (Reel 37, Frame 206)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1959/405.S
      - University of Edinburgh (Social Anthropology) (Reel 37, Frame 209)
  - Wales, 1959/407
    - University College (N-S) (Reel 37, Frame 212)
    - Wales - Medical Sciences, 1959/407.A
      - Welsh National School of Medicine (Reel 37, Frame 219)
  - Malta, 1959/409
    Malta
    - Malta - Fellowships, 1959/409.E
      - Zahra, Albert (Reel 37, Frame 237)
    - Malta - Declinations, 1959/409.F
      - K-U (Reel 37, Frame 242)
  - Australia, 1959/410
    - 410 (Reel 37, Frame 246)
    - A-T (Reel 37, Frame 257)
    - U-V (Reel 37, Frame 358)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1959/410.A
      - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 456)
    - Australia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/410.D
      - University of Queensland (Agriculture) (Reel 37, Frame 553)
    - Australia - Fellowships, 1959/410.E
      - J-M (Reel 37, Frame 556)
    - Australia - Declinations, 1959/410.F
      - Nadel, George H. (Reel 37, Frame 662)
  - New Zealand, 1959/418
    - A-U (Reel 37, Frame 681)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1959/418.A
      - University of Otago (Medical School) (Reel 37, Frame 731)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, 1959/418.E
      - Beer, Colin G. (Reel 37, Frame 747)
  - Fiji, 1959/419
    - Fiji - Medical Sciences, 1959/419.A
      - Central Medical School (Reel 37, Frame 767)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1959/420
    - C-W (Reel 37, Frame 769)
  - Guyana, 1959/423
    - B-S (Reel 37, Frame 838)
    - Guyana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/423.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 37, Frame 856)
  - Canada, 1959/427
    - A-N (Reel 37, Frame 858)
    - R-U (Reel 37, Frame 1120)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1959/427.A
      - D-U (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1959/427.R
      - P-U (Reel 38, Frame 55)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1959/427.S
      - Laval University (Social Sciences) (Reel 38, Frame 74)
  - Jamaica, 1959/437
    - A-U (Reel 38, Frame 76)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1959/437.A
      - University College of the West Indies (M-P) (Reel 38, Frame 94)
    - Jamaica - Humanities and Arts, 1959/437.R
      - University College of the West Indies (Linguistics) (Reel 38, Frame 97)
  - Trinidad, 1959/451
    - G-S (Reel 38, Frame 112)
  - Ceylon, 1959/462
    - B-W (Reel 38, Frame 212)
    - Ceylon - Fellowships, 1959/462.E
      - B-S (Reel 38, Frame 271)
    - Ceylon - Humanities and Arts, 1959/462.R
      - Drama (Reel 38, Frame 280)
  - Hong Kong, 1959/463
    - C-U (Reel 38, Frame 290)
  - India, 1959/464
    - 464 (Reel 38, Frame 324)
    - A (Reel 38, Frame 333)
    - B-C (Reel 38, Frame 364)
    - D-E (Reel 38, Frame 690)
    - Finance (Desai, Morarji) (Reel 38, Frame 778)
    - F-H (Reel 38, Frame 1021)
    - Indian (A-S) (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - I-K (Reel 39, Frame 142)
    - L-M (Reel 39, Frame 227)
    - N-P (Reel 39, Frame 381)
    - Q-S (Reel 39, Frame 632)
    - T-V (Reel 39, Frame 915)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1959/464.A
      - A-V (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - India - Nursing, 1959/464.C
      - 464C (Reel 40, Frame 88)
      - A-V (Reel 40, Frame 115)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/464.D
      - 464D (Reel 40, Frame 134)
      - A-T (Reel 40, Frame 136)
    - India - Fellowships, 1959/464.E
      - 464E (Reel 40, Frame 200)
      - A-V (Reel 40, Frame 249)
    - India - Declinations, 1959/464.F
      - Nath, Ravindra (Reel 40, Frame 391)
    - India - Malaria, 1959/464.I
      - 464I (Reel 40, Frame 394)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1959/464.R
      - L-U (Reel 40, Frame 411)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1959/464.S
      - 464S (Reel 40, Frame 487)
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 489)
  - Pakistan, 1959/465
    - 465 (Reel 40, Frame 517)
    - A-Z (Reel 40, Frame 521)
    - Pakistan - Medical Sciences, 1959/465.A
      - Pakistan Medical Association (Ali, Manawar) (Reel 40, Frame 596)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, 1959/465.E
      - 465E (Reel 40, Frame 598)
      - A-R (Reel 40, Frame 616)
    - Pakistan - Social Sciences, 1959/465.S
      - 465S (Reel 40, Frame 733)
      - I-U (Reel 40, Frame 735)
  - Burma, 1959/468
    - 468 (Reel 40, Frame 749)
    - B-W (Reel 40, Frame 751)
    - Burma - Social Sciences, 1959/468.S
      - University of Rangoon (Social Sciences) (Reel 40, Frame 766)
  - Iraq, 1959/470
    - 470 (Reel 40, Frame 778)
    - Administration (Reel 40, Frame 781)
    - Listed Mail (Reel 40, Frame 786)
    - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 793)
  - Malaysia, 1959/473
    - L-U (Reel 40, Frame 877)
    - Malaysia - Fellowships, 1959/473.E
      - Ho, Wing-men (Reel 40, Frame 894)
  - Africa, 1959/475
    - 475 (Reel 40, Frame 897)
    - A-E (Reel 40, Frame 919)
    - Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/475.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1959/475.R
      - 475R (Reel 41, Frame 8)
  - East Africa Region, 1959/477
    - A-W (Reel 41, Frame 13)
    - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1959/477.A
      - Makerere College (Medical School) (Reel 41, Frame 143)
    - East Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/477.D
      - E-M (Reel 41, Frame 153)
    - East Africa Region - Fellowships, 1959/477.E
      - H-N (Reel 41, Frame 258)
  - North Africa Region, 1959/485
    - 485 (Reel 41, Frame 271)
    - A-T (Reel 41, Frame 276)
    - North Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1959/485.A
      - Kitchener School of Medicine (Reel 41, Frame 359)
    - North Africa Region - Nursing, 1959/485.C
      - 485C (Reel 41, Frame 363)
      - Alexandria University (Nursing School) (Reel 41, Frame 368)
    - North Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/485.D
      - A-S (Reel 41, Frame 370)
  - South Africa Region, 1959/487
    - 487 (Reel 41, Frame 373)
    - Listed Mail (Reel 41, Frame 380)
    - A-V (Reel 41, Frame 398)
    - South Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1959/487.A
      - University (C-W) (Reel 41, Frame 607)
    - South Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/487.D
      - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland (Boughey, A. S.) (Reel 41, Frame 743)
    - South Africa Region - Fellowships, 1959/487.E
      - A-W (Reel 41, Frame 745)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1959/489
    South Africa
    - du Preez, Louis J. (Reel 41, Frame 763)
  - Uganda, 1959/492
    Uganda
    - Makerere College (History) (Reel 41, Frame 769)
  - West Africa, 1959/495
    - 495 (Reel 41, Frame 771)
    - A-I (Reel 41, Frame 785)
    - J-T (Reel 41, Frame 909)
    - U-W (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - West Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/495.D
      - G-N (Reel 42, Frame 281)
    - West Africa - Fellowships, 1959/495.E
      - A-R (Reel 42, Frame 307)
    - West Africa - Declinations, 1959/495.F
      - Wodiong, Okon (Reel 42, Frame 336)
  - Nigeria, 1959/497
    - University College, Ibadan (O-P) (Reel 42, Frame 344)
  - France, 1959/500
    - A-G (Reel 42, Frame 347)
    - H-M (Reel 42, Frame 488)
    - N-W (Reel 42, Frame 581)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1959/500.A
      - M-U (Reel 42, Frame 872)
    - France - Fellowships, 1959/500.E
      - E-R (Reel 42, Frame 893)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1959/500.R
      - 500R (Reel 42, Frame 916)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1959/500.S
      - 500S (Reel 42, Frame 919)
  - French Guiana, 1959/507
    French Guiana
    - Laye, Camere (Reel 42, Frame 922)
  - Vietnam, 1959/509
    - Vietnamese-American Association (Reel 42, Frame 924)
    - Vietnam - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/509.D
      - Vietnam (Agriculture) (Reel 42, Frame 926)
    - Vietnam - Fellowships, 1959/509.E
      - 509E (Reel 42, Frame 929)
  - Cambodia, 1959/513
    - C-E (Reel 42, Frame 931)
    - Cambodia - Fellowships, 1959/513.E
      - D-H (Reel 42, Frame 942)
  - Ivory Coast, 1959/527
    - Center for Advanced Studies, Abidjan (Reel 42, Frame 953)
    - Ivory Coast - Humanities and Arts, 1959/527.R
      - Drama (Gadeau, Coffi) (Reel 42, Frame 967)
  - Asia, 1959/600
    - Administration (Reel 42, Frame 971)
    - Colombo Plan (Reel 42, Frame 1117)
    - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1959/600.R
      - 600R (Reel 42, Frame 1123)
  - China, 1959/601
    - B-T (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1959/601.A
      - Medical Education (Reel 43, Frame 44)
  - Taiwan, 1959/605
    - A-Y (Reel 43, Frame 46)
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1959/605.C
      - 605C (Reel 43, Frame 80)
  - Japan, 1959/609
    - 609 (Reel 43, Frame 86)
    - A-E (Reel 43, Frame 257)
    - F-H (Reel 43, Frame 372)
    - I-J (Reel 43, Frame 524)
    - Ka-Ke (Reel 43, Frame 646)
    - Ki-Ky (Reel 43, Frame 756)
    - M-O (Reel 43, Frame 947)
    - P-S (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Tokyo (C-W) (Reel 44, Frame 129)
    - T (Reel 44, Frame 304)
    - U-Y (Reel 44, Frame 451)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1959/609.A
      - C-T (Reel 44, Frame 506)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1959/609.C
      - 609C (Reel 44, Frame 535)
      - S-T (Reel 44, Frame 551)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/609.D
      - A-O (Reel 44, Frame 598)
    - Japan - Fellowships, 1959/609.E
      - 609E (Reel 44, Frame 628)
      - A-N (Reel 44, Frame 688)
      - O-Y (Reel 44, Frame 905)
    - Japan - Declinations, 1959/609.F
      - Mikami, Shin-ichi (Reel 44, Frame 1046)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1959/609.R
      - 609R (Reel 44, Frame 1068)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1959/609.S
      - 609S (Reel 44, Frame 1071)
      - I-W (Reel 44, Frame 1073)
  - Korea, 1959/613
    - 613 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - C-Y (Reel 45, Frame 23)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1959/613.R
      - Libraries (Reel 45, Frame 114)
  - Thailand, 1959/617
    - C-Y (Reel 45, Frame 116)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1959/617.A
      - University of Medical Sciences (D-S) (Reel 45, Frame 170)
    - Thailand - Nursing, 1959/617.C
      - 617C (Reel 45, Frame 194)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/617.D
      - Agriculture (Chakrabandhu) (Reel 45, Frame 200)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1959/617.E
      - C (Reel 45, Frame 204)
  - Southeast Asia, 1959/625
    - Association of Southeast Asian Institutions of Higher Learning (Reel 45, Frame 217)
  - Holland, 1959/650
    - B-W (Reel 45, Frame 219)
    - Holland - Fellowships, 1959/650.E
      - D-S (Reel 45, Frame 415)
  - Indonesia, 1959/652
    - 652 (Reel 45, Frame 422)
    - A-G (Reel 45, Frame 430)
    - H-P (Reel 45, Frame 577)
    - S-W (Reel 45, Frame 738)
    - Indonesia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/652.D
      - University of Indonesia (Agriculture) (Reel 45, Frame 890)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1959/652.E
      - 652E (Reel 45, Frame 896)
      - A-W (Reel 45, Frame 935)
  - Surinam, 1959/659
    Suriname
    - Health (Reel 45, Frame 984)
  - Europe, 1959/700
    - C-E (Reel 45, Frame 995)
    - Europe - Humanities and Arts, 1959/700.R
      - 700R (Reel 45, Frame 1140)
  - Ethiopia, 1959/701
    - Ethiopia - Medical Sciences, 1959/701.E
      - Gebre-Mariam, Berhane (Reel 45, Frame 1160)
  - Afghanistan, 1959/703
    - Foreign Affairs (Reel 45, Frame 1170)
    - Afghanistan - Medical Sciences, 1959/703.A
      - Kabul University (Medical School) (Reel 45, Frame 1175)
  - Austria, 1959/705
    - A-V (Reel 46, Frame 1)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1959/705.E
      - K-M (Reel 46, Frame 133)
  - Belgium, 1959/707
    - B-V (Reel 46, Frame 138)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1959/707.C
      - University of Brussels (Reel 46, Frame 269)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, 1959/707.E
      - H-V (Reel 46, Frame 273)
  - Yugoslavia, 1959/710
    - B-Y (Reel 46, Frame 294)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, 1959/710.E
      - A-V (Reel 46, Frame 311)
    - Yugoslavia - Social Sciences, 1959/710.S
      - Institute of Social Sciences, Belgrade (Reel 46, Frame 330)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1959/712
    Slovakia; Czech Republic
    - B-H (Reel 46, Frame 335)
  - Denmark, 1959/713
    - B-U (Reel 46, Frame 348)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, 1959/713.E
      - Foget, Maja Edel (Reel 46, Frame 408)
    - Denmark - Declinations, 1959/713.F
      - Prasse, K. G. (Reel 46, Frame 410)
  - Estonia, 1959/714
    Estonia
    - Martin, Alma (Reel 46, Frame 416)
  - Iceland, 1959/715
    - 715 (Reel 46, Frame 419)
    - University of Iceland (Sigurdsson, Bjorn) (Reel 46, Frame 424)
  - Germany, 1959/717
    - A-L (Reel 46, Frame 427)
    - S-W (Reel 46, Frame 598)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1959/717.A
      - Free University of Berlin (Medical School) (Reel 46, Frame 810)
    - Germany - Nursing, 1959/717.C
      - University of Heidelberg (Nursing) (Reel 46, Frame 813)
    - Germany - Fellowships, 1959/717.E
      - D-W (Reel 46, Frame 819)
    - Germany - Declinations, 1959/717.F
      - Friedrich Ebert Foundation (Reel 46, Frame 845)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1959/717.S
      - University of Freiburg (Political Science) (Reel 46, Frame 869)
  - Greece, 1959/749
    - 749 (Reel 46, Frame 871)
    - A-U (Reel 46, Frame 873)
    - Greece - Medical Sciences, 1959/749.A
      - University of Athens (Reel 46, Frame 915)
    - Greece - Fellowships, 1959/749.E
      - Nianias, Demetrius Geord (Reel 46, Frame 927)
  - Hungary, 1959/750
    - 750 (Reel 46, Frame 930)
    - A-Z (Reel 46, Frame 932)
  - Italy, 1959/751
    - B-P (Reel 46, Frame 977)
    - R-Z (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1959/751.A
      - Catholic University, Rome (Reel 47, Frame 243)
    - Italy - Fellowships, 1959/751.E
      - C-S (Reel 47, Frame 281)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1959/751.S
      - Universita Commerciale Luigi Bocconi (Economics) (Reel 47, Frame 322)
  - Liberia, 1959/759
    Liberia
    - Foreign Ministry (Reel 47, Frame 324)
  - Norway, 1959/767
    - A-U (Reel 47, Frame 329)
    - Norway - Fellowships, 1959/767.E
      - A-W (Reel 47, Frame 372)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1959/767.S
      - Institute for Social Research, Oslo (Reel 47, Frame 383)
  - Iran, 1959/771
    - B-U (Reel 47, Frame 403)
    - Iran - Medical Sciences, 1959/771.A
      - University of Teheran (Medical School) (Reel 47, Frame 820)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1959/771.C
      - Shiraz School of Nursing (Reel 47, Frame 842)
  - Portugal, 1959/773
    - G-O (Reel 47, Frame 896)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1959/773.C
      - School of Nursing (Reel 47, Frame 932)
  - Romania, 1959/783
    - Cioran, E. M. (Reel 47, Frame 934)
  - Russia, 1959/785
    - 785 (Reel 47, Frame 939)
    - K-V (Reel 47, Frame 1027)
  - Finland, 1959/787
    - P-U (Reel 47, Frame 1126)
    - Finland - Fellowships, 1959/787.E
      - K (Reel 47, Frame 1132)
  - Lithuania, 1959/788
    Lithuania
    - Zakevicius, Stasys (Reel 47, Frame 1146)
  - Poland, 1959/789
    - 789 (Reel 47, Frame 1148)
    - A-Z (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1959/789.A
      - University of Lodz (Physiology) (Reel 48, Frame 202)
    - Poland - Nursing, 1959/789.C
      - 789C (Reel 48, Frame 206)
      - P-W (Reel 48, Frame 230)
    - Poland - Fellowships, 1959/789.E
      - 789E (Reel 48, Frame 253)
      - A-Z (Reel 48, Frame 305)
  - Spain, 1959/795
    - L-U (Reel 48, Frame 573)
  - Sweden, 1959/800
    - B-W (Reel 48, Frame 588)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1959/800.A
      - University of Lund (Medical Clinic) (Reel 48, Frame 672)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, 1959/800.E
      - B-V (Reel 48, Frame 680)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1959/800.S
      - Gothenburg Institute of International Relations (Reel 48, Frame 725)
  - Switzerland, 1959/803
    - B-U (Reel 48, Frame 727)
    - Switzerland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/803.D
      - University of Berne (Theodor Kocher Institute) (Reel 48, Frame 830)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, 1959/803.E
      - Geiger, Willi (Reel 48, Frame 833)
  - Near East Region, 1959/804
    - 804 (Reel 48, Frame 837)
    - Baghdad Pact Nuclear Centre (McKay, H. A. C.) (Reel 48, Frame 839)
  - Turkey, 1959/805
    - 805 (Reel 48, Frame 844)
    - A-S (Reel 48, Frame 846)
    - T-Z (Reel 48, Frame 1054)
    - Turkey - Medical Sciences, 1959/805.A
      - I-M (Reel 49, Frame 1)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, 1959/805.E
      - 805E (Reel 49, Frame 19)
      - A-R (Reel 49, Frame 21)
  - Crete, 1959/807
    Crete
    - Committee for the Development of Crete (Reel 49, Frame 53)
  - Egypt, 1959/812
    Egypt
    - 812 (Reel 49, Frame 55)
    - A-V (Reel 49, Frame 57)
    - Egypt - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1959/812.D
      - Agriculture (Mahrouki, A.) (Reel 49, Frame 105)
    - Egypt - Fellowships, 1959/812.E
      - I-K (Reel 49, Frame 108)
  - Jordan, 1959/816
    - H-M (Reel 49, Frame 142)
  - Aden, 1959/818
    Yemen (Republic)
    - Vianney, John J. (Reel 49, Frame 177)
  - Israel, 1959/825
    - 825 (Reel 49, Frame 182)
    - C-S (Reel 49, Frame 185)
    - Israel - Fellowships, 1959/825.E
      - Nevo, Abraham C. (Reel 49, Frame 227)
  - Lebanon, 1959/833
    - A-U (Reel 49, Frame 235)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, 1959/833.E
      - H-N (Reel 49, Frame 519)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1959/833.C
      - American University of Beirut (Nursing School) (Reel 49, Frame 514)
  - Program and Policy, 1959/900
    - Administration (Reel 49, Frame 587)
  - Members and Meetings, 1959/903
    - Bingham, Barry (Reel 49, Frame 664)
    - Bowles, Chester (Reel 49, Frame 678)
    - Brace, Lloyd D. (Reel 49, Frame 726)
    - Bradfield, Richard (Reel 49, Frame 733)
    - Bronk, Detlev W. (Reel 49, Frame 799)
    - Bunche, Ralph J. (Reel 49, Frame 817)
    - Dickey, John S. (Reel 49, Frame 828)
    - Douglas, Lewis W. (Reel 49, Frame 843)
    - DuBridge, Lee A. (Reel 49, Frame 857)
    - Harrison, Wallace K. (Reel 49, Frame 864)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr. (Reel 49, Frame 872)
    - Kerr, Clark (Reel 49, Frame 891)
    - Kimberly, John R. (Reel 49, Frame 898)
    - Loeb, Robert F. (Reel 49, Frame 911)
    - Lovett, Robert A. (Reel 49, Frame 928)
    - McKelway, Benjamin M. (Reel 49, Frame 944)
    - Members and Meetings (Notices) (Reel 49, Frame 951)
    - Members and Meetings (Out of Town Meeting Arrangements) (Reel 49, Frame 1036)
    - Moe, Henry A. (Reel 49, Frame 1061)
    - Parran, Thomas (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Reel 50, Frame 33)
    - Van Dusen, Henry P. (Reel 50, Frame 68)
    - Wood, W. Barry, Jr. (Reel 50, Frame 77)
  - Agriculture, 1959/923
    - Consultants (Candidates) (Reel 50, Frame 99)
    - Consultants (B-Y) (Reel 50, Frame 114)
    - Staff Candidates (Viets, Frank G.) (Reel 50, Frame 356)
- General Correspondence, 1960
  - International, 1960/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Allen, LeRoy R. (Reel 1, Frame 90)
    - Anderson, Charles R. (Reel 1, Frame 169)
    - Anderson, Richmond K. (Reel 1, Frame 268)
    - Atlantic Institute (Reel 1, Frame 297)
    - Baird, Guy B. (Reel 1, Frame 420)